

Hafiz Javaid Web Developer

Street 62, G-11/2, Islamabad

☑ hafizjaidi786@gmail.com

& +92 343 56877704

SOCIAL

in Hafiz Jawaid Iqbal

f Hafiz Jawaid Iqbal

(iii) Hafiz Javaid Iqbal

PROFILE

I am a developer with an engineering mind and creativity is my passion. I am self-disciplined, highly motivated, having multitasking ability with polished technical skills.

I have experience in the freelance market as well as working with a small startup as a front end developer

SKILLS

- Html
- Vue
- Css
- React
- Saas
- Javascript

EDUCATION

Software Engineering

UET Taxila, Pakistan 2018 - Present

FSc (Pre-Engineering)

Sir Sayed College, Rawalpindi 2016 - 2018

EXPERIENCE

RigRex / Front-end Developer

2019 - PRESENT

Working as a Front-end developer at RigRex. Primary responsibilities are to develop the Front-end of Websites.

STIC (Software Engineer)

Sep 2018 - 2019

I worked as a software eningeer at stic.

CERTIFICATES

Member of Hackathon Winner Team AirTech'19

We Presented the idea of a Forest fire prevention system using WSN.

LANGUAGES

English

- Panjabi
- Urdu

INTERESTS

X

Travel 6

Gaming

Reading